♪I lament on the cruel and untimely love♪
أنا أتحسر على الحب القاسي والغير أوانه ♪
♪Yet I come to realise it's a daydream when the bubbles burst♪
♪ ومع ذلك أدركت أنه حلم يقظة عندما تنفجر الفقاعات ♪
♪A city of spring flowers♪
♪ مدينة زهور الربيع ♪
♪Sinks into the indifferent autumnal frost♪
♪ يغرق في الصقيع الخريفي غير المبال
♪A snowflake falls into the river♪
♪ تسقط ندفة ثلجية في النهر ♪
♪The biting cold stalks over♪
♪ السيقان الباردة القارضة
♪All assumptions are nothing♪
كل الافتراضات لا شيء
♪But a disguised makeup♪
♪ لكن مكياج مقنع
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the passionate gaze behind the mask♪
♪ للنظرة العاطفية خلف القناع ♪
♪Love and hate are the most unforgettable feelings♪
الحب والكراهية من أكثر المشاعر التي لا تنسى
♪Overwhelmed by my longings♪
غارقة في شوقي ♪
♪I tear off those old scores♪
♪ مزقت تلك الدرجات القديمة ♪
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the irretrievable past♪
إلى الماضي الذي لا يمكن استرجاعه ♪
=Little Mad Doctor=
= الطبيب المجنون الصغير =
=Episode 3=
= الحلقة 3 =
(This man is so outstanding,)
(هذا الرجل رائع جدا)
(sadly, he's a eunuch.)
(للأسف ، إنه خصي.)
(He must be in agony.)
(يجب أن يكون في عذاب).
(Why did I sense)
(لماذا شعرت)
(a tinge of pity from her eyes?)
(مسحة شفقة من عينيها؟)
You're so good looking.
أنت جيد المظهر.
Why do you wear a mask?
لماذا ترتدي القناع؟
Eunuch Ye.
أيها الخصي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You may go back now, Your Highness.
يمكنك العودة الآن ، صاحب السمو.
Lord War said
قال اللورد الحرب
it's not necessary for you to return here
ليس من الضروري أن تعود إلى هنا
if you can simply leave here as you wish.
إذا كان يمكنك ببساطة المغادرة من هنا كما يحلو لك.
We never shelter idlers
نحن لا نؤوي الراكلين
(Longsan) or good-for-nothing.
(Longsan) أو خير مقابل لا شيء.
Tell Lord War
أخبر اللورد الحرب
that I'm not going to leave this place.
أنني لن أغادر هذا المكان.
Princess Jinghong.
الأميرة جينغهونغ.
No one is allowed
لا يسمح لأحد
to enter the study without permission.
للدخول إلى الدراسة دون إذن.
Please return to your room.
يرجى العودة إلى غرفتك.
Return?
يعود؟
To where?
إلى أين؟
Fusheng Abode of Suoqing Palace
منزل فوشينغ في قصر Suoqing
or the guest room here?
أو غرفة الضيوف هنا؟
Let her in.
دعها تدخل.
I don't care if you chuck me out.
لا يهمني إذا طردتني.
Give me back my things
أعد لي أشيائي
and this is our farewell.
وهذا وداعنا.
Give it back to me.
أعدها الي.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
You're not so dense after all.
أنت لست كثيفًا جدًا بعد كل شيء.
My Lord.
ربي.
I have no one to rely on
ليس لدي من أعتمد عليه
and I always got bullied
ودائما ما أتعرض للتنمر
in Suoqing Palace.
في قصر Suoqing.
I wish I could never
اتمنى لو لم استطع ابدا
return to that ruddy place.
العودة إلى ذلك المكان الأحمر.
My Lord, I beg of you.
ربي اتوسل اليك.
Please take me in.
من فضلك خذني.
I'm willing
أرغب
to do everything
أن تفعل كل شيء
you ask.
أنت تسأل.
Everything?
كل شئ؟
No...not really.
لا ليس بالفعل كذلك.
You may stay at Hanlu Abode.
يمكنك البقاء في Hanlu Abode.
All right.
حسنًا.
No way.
مستحيل.
The credit for saving a person is so little?
الفضل لإنقاذ شخص ضئيل جدا؟
When can I return to the real world then?
متى يمكنني العودة إلى العالم الحقيقي بعد ذلك؟
Wen.
ون.
How come that stupid Chu Jinghong hasn't been kicked out by Lord War yet?
لماذا لم يتم طرد تشو جينغ هونغ الغبي من قبل حرب اللورد حتى الآن؟
Lord War will never like her.
لورد وور لن تحبها أبدًا.
What if Lord War sees her true countenance?
ماذا لو رأت لورد وور وجهها الحقيقي؟
Wen.
ون.
Did I see it wrong?
هل رأيت ذلك خطأ؟
All men will definitely
كل الرجال بالتأكيد
swoon over her beauty.
إغماء على جمالها.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Chu Jinghong is doing something.
يقوم Chu Jinghong بعمل شيء ما.
Does she?
هل هي؟
She brought along some weird stuff
لقد أحضرت بعض الأشياء الغريبة
and set up a healing kiosk on the street.
وأنشأوا كشكًا للشفاء في الشارع.
However, the way she treats patients seems strange.
ومع ذلك ، فإن الطريقة التي تعامل بها المرضى تبدو غريبة.
(Cheng'er)
(شنغر)
I have never seen it before.
(Cheng'er) لم أره من قبل.
Chu Jinghong.
تشو جينغهونغ.
I will prevent you from getting close to Lord War.
سأمنعك من الاقتراب من حرب اللورد.
Everyone.
الجميع.
Please queue in line.
الرجاء الانتظار في الطابور.
(Jin'er)
(جينير)
You just got a little feverish.
لقد أصبت قليلا بالحمى.
It will be recovered by taking medicine.
سيتم شفائه عن طريق تناول الدواء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Chu Jinghong.
تشو جينغهونغ.
How shameless of you.
كيف وقح منكم.
How could you do this in the public?
كيف يمكنك فعل هذا في الأماكن العامة؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I set up a mobile clinic
أنشأت عيادة متنقلة
and the treatment is free of charge.
والعلاج مجاني.
Why am I shameless?
لماذا انا وقح؟
You!
أنت!
What are you up to?
ما آخر ما توصلت اليه؟
If you're doing this to please me
إذا كنت تفعل هذا لإرضاء لي
and marry you,
وأتزوجك ،
that's never going to happen.
لن يحدث هذا أبدًا.
I shall thank you for not marrying me.
سوف أشكرك لأنك لم تتزوجني.
What did you just say?
ماذا قلت للتو؟
A few days ago,
منذ بضعة أيام،
you gave away me to Lord War
لقد أعطيتني للورد الحرب
because you couldn't pay ten thousand silver taels.
لأنك لا تستطيع دفع عشرة آلاف تايل فضي.
You seem to have forgotten this already.
يبدو أنك نسيت هذا بالفعل.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
I think
أظن
I belong to Lord War, right?
أنا أنتمي إلى Lord War ، أليس كذلك؟
Chu Jinghong.
تشو جينغهونغ.
Quit talking nonsense.
توقف عن الحديث الهراء.
There's no way
ليس هناك طريقة
you can be the consort of Lord War.
يمكنك أن تكون رفيق Lord War.
I never want to marry Lord War.
أنا لا أريد الزواج من لورد وور.
It was Second Prince who gave me away
كان الأمير الثاني هو من وهبني
because of ten thousand silver taels.
بسبب عشرة آلاف تايل فضي.
I was there that day.
كنت هناك في ذلك اليوم.
It wasn't like what you said.
لم يكن مثل ما قلته.
I wonder what was it like that day.
أتساءل كيف كان ذلك اليوم.
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد
♪Hair turns grey in one winter night♪
♪ يتحول لون الشعر إلى اللون الرمادي في ليلة شتاء ♪
♪The appearance remains in spite of the thick frost♪
المظهر يبقى بالرغم من الصقيع الكثيف
♪Time slips by in that dream-like world♪
♪ الوقت يمر في هذا العالم الذي يشبه الحلم
♪Life is always full of splendor♪
♪ الحياة دائما مليئة بالروعة
♪We part when the flowers fall♪
♪ نفترق عندما تسقط الأزهار
♪Desolate chills blow away several autumns♪
♪ قشعريرة مقفرة تهب عدة خريفات ♪
♪Eternal love is all I seek♪
الحب الأبدي هو كل ما أسعى إليه
♪Though the sweet dream fades at last♪
رغم أن الحلم الجميل يتلاشى أخيرًا ♪
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد